One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Lion
اللبوة
Bege!
بيجي
Oh, no! Brother Oven is furious!
مصيبة، أخي أوفن غاضب
Get to the port!
توجهوا إلى الميناء
There's nowhere to run on the sea!
لا مفرّ لكم على البحر
Nor on the land!
ولا على اليابسة
Get off the ship!
انزلوا من سفينتكم
So you chose to fight, Bege!
إذًا اخترت القتال يا بيجي؟
All right. I'll execute you now!
لا بأس، سوف أعدمك
This is bad, Big Sis! We can't set sail!
ما العمل يا أختي؟ لا يمكننا الإبحار
What should we do with the cake?!
ما الذي سنفعله بالكعكة؟
Increase our speed!
أسرعوا
Go straight to the port!
تقدّموا مباشرة إلى الميناء
Bege's ship sped up!
سفينة بيجي زادت من سرعتها
What is he thinking?! He's gonna crash into the port!
ما الذي يفكر به؟ سيصطدم بالميناء
Why isn't he slowing down?!
لماذا لم يخففوا من سرعتهم؟
Don't tell me... it's a suicide attack?!
أيعقل أنّه هجوم انتحاري؟
It's sailing onto the coast!
إنّها تصعد إلى اليابسة
Bege!
بيجي
Don't hold back! Get ready to shoot!
لا تتراجعوا، استعدوا للإطلاق
You traitor!
أيها الخائن
How about this, you little punks?
ابتعدوا عن طريقي أيها الإخوة الصغار
This ship, the Nostra Castello...
...إنّ سفينة نوسترا كاستيلو هذه
can sail on both water and land!
هي سفينة برمائية
Bege!
بيجي
The paddles turned into tank caterpillars!
تحولت المجاديف إلى جنازير دبابة
I didn't think that was even possible!
لم أسمع أنّك تملك حيلة كهذه
That's because I never told you!
هذا لأنني لم أخبركم عنها
Why would I show all my tricks to the people I had already decided to betray?!
ولِمَ عساي أكشف أسراري للأشخاص الذين أنوي خيانتهم؟
You scumbag!
لا تعبث معنا
Shoot-rero !
أطلقوا-ريرو
Chiffon! Hand the cake over to us!
شيفون، ضعوا الكعكة على سفينتنا
What?!
ماذا؟
That's impossible! The cake is gigantic!
هذا ضربٌ من الجنون، فالكعكة ضخمة
How are we going to hand such a big cake over to a ship moving that fast?!
كيف يمكن وضعها على سفينة تسير بهذه السرعة؟
What?! Whaaat?!
ماذا؟ ماذا؟
What's happening?!
ما الذي يحدث؟
What?!
ماذا؟
Black Leg!
الساق السوداء
Make room on the deck, Bege!
أخلوا سطح السفينة يا بيجي
Sanji-san !
سانجي-سان
Madam Pudding!
بودينغ-ساما
Hurry up, Bege!
أسرع يا بيجي
Step back, guys!
تراجعوا يا رفاق
Make room on the deck!
أخلوا سطح السفينة
Y-Yes, Father!
حـ-حاضر يا فاذر
Black Leg... All right, come aboard!
أيها الساق السوداء، هيّا تعال
Who the hell is that?!
من يكون هذا يا تُرى؟
He's using just one leg...
إنّه يرفعها بساق واحدة
Okay! Let's go!
حسنًا، هيّا بنا
Everyone! Brace for impact!
استعدوا جميعًا للهبوط
The cake made it aboard!
هبطت الكعكة بسلام
That was amazing, Black Leg!
مذهل أيها الساق السوداء
What is this wonderful fragrance?
ما هذه الرائحة الزكية؟
A-As expected of Germa!
كـ-كما هو متوقع من أحد الجيرما
I'm not a member of Germa!
أنا لست من الجيرما
Bege! Pez!
بيجي، بيز
Are you alright, honey?
هل أنتِ بخير يا عزيزتي؟
Yes...
أجل
You've always been so reckless...
يا لك من متهوّر حقًّا
Thank you!
شكرًا لك
Madam Pudding! Stay with us!
بودينغ-ساما، تماسكي
I'm not gonna let them get away!
لن أدعكم تلوذون بالفرار
Watch out!
احذر
Minister Oven! Please get out of the way!
أوفن-ساما، ابتعد عن الطريق رجاءً
Don't you know who I am?!
ألا تدركون من أنا؟
I'll stop them!
سأوقفها
SQUISH!
سحق
He got run over!
لقد دُعس
Oh, there there, Pez. It was a little loud back there, right?
هوّن عليك يا بيز، أكان الأمر صاخبًا عليك؟
He's still there...
ما زال هناك
Who is that guy? Is he a pervert?
من يكون ذلك الشخص؟ أهو منحرف؟
Huh? What's the matter, Pez?
ما الخطب يا بيز؟
It looks like she's happy.
إنّها تبدو سعيدة
We need to sail toward the southeastern sea, Bege!
نريد أن نبحر باتجاه الجنوب الشرقي يا بيجي
Okay...
أجل
Pudding!
بودينغ
We'll have to run over a few chocolate houses.
سنضطر لسحق بعض منازل بلدة الشوكولاتة
What?!
ماذا؟
That's the only way for us to depart safely!
إنها تضحية ضرورية ما دام الأمر سيتيح لنا الهرب جميعًا
What a waste.
يا للأسف
I'll fix them later.
سأصلحها لاحقًا
Houses can be rebuilt. And so can families.
يمكن الحصول على منازل جديدة، وكذلك «العائلات»، صحيح؟
Yeah. It'd be better if they didn't break apart, but...
هذا صحيح، لكن يفضّل ألّا تتحطم بالطبع
this is my home now.
ولكن هنا حيث أنتمي الآن
And you guys are my new family.
ولدي عائلة جديدة فيها الكثير من الأفراد
Madam!
سيدتنا
You bastards!
أيها الأوغاد
Stop using the cannon!
لا تستخدم القذائف
You might blow up the cake!
لا نريد تفجير الكعكة
They're gonna get to the sea! Don't let them escape!
إنّهم على وشك الوصول إلى البحر، لا تدعوهم يفلتوا
Fleet! Head for the southeastern side of the island!
أيها الأسطول، توجهوا نحو الجنوب الشرقي من الجزيرة
We're on our way!
نحن في الطريق
All right! We made it off Cacao Island!
عظيم، خرجنا من جزيرة الكاكاو
Hooray!
مرحى
No one can catch up to this paddle ship now.
لا أحد يستطيع اللحاق بسفينة المجاديف الآن
Thanks, Bege. You saved us.
شكرًا لك يا بيجي، لقد أنقذتنا
I didn't do it for your sake, Black Leg!
لم أفعل هذا من أجلكم أيها الساق السوداء
Isn't it oddly hot over here?
أليس الطقس حارًّا جدًّا؟
Father, the sea looks weird-rero !
فاذر، البحر يبدو غريبًا-ريرو
Fish are floating to the surface!
الأسماك تطفو على السطح
The sea is so hot that it boiled them?!
أهي تغلي بالماء الساخن؟
With the right amount of salt, they'd probably taste good...
قد يكون طعمها لذيذًا إن أضفنا إليها بعض الملح
We're gonna be next, you idiot!
سنغلي معها أيها الأحمق
There's only one person capable of this...
ثمة شخص واحد قادر على فعل هذا
Look!
انظروا
Hot Sea Hell!
بحر الجحيم الساخن نيكاي جيغوكو
I will boil you all to death!
سأغليكم حتّى الموت أيها الأوغاد
It's hot!
يا للحرارة
It's simmering-rero !
إننا نغلي-ريرو
We have a bigger issue to worry about!
لدينا مشاكل أخرى
This is bad! This'll affect the temperature of the chocolate!
مصيبة، ستؤثر درجة الحرارة على الشوكولاتة
The whipped cream will melt, too!
والكريمة المخفوقة ستذوب أيضًا
That means...
...ذلك يعني
...if nothing is done, Big Mom's cake will be ruined!
على هذا المعدّل، ستفسد الكعكة التي أعددناها لبيغ مام
That idiot, what is he thinking?!
ذلك الأحمق، ما الذي يفكر به؟
Big Mom won't be satisfied with boiled fish!
السمك المسلوق لن يُرضي بيغ مام
What happened?!
ما الذي يحدث؟
The heat broke the paddles!
أحد مجاديف السفينة قد تحطّم بسبب الحرارة
Rero-rero ! Is he planning on sinking our ship?!
ريرو-ريرو، هل ينوي إغراق سفينتنا؟
Did Minister Oven forget how important this cake is?!
هل نسي أوفن-ساما مدى أهمية هذه الكعكة؟
It's okay...
لا بأس
It's gonna be okay...
كل شيء سيكون على ما يرام
Sink...
اغرقوا
You're acting strange... Why have you been laughing so much, Pez?
أنت تتصرّف بغرابة، لِمَ تضحك فجأة يا بيز؟
Who the hell are you?
من أنت يا هذا؟
Minister Oven! Watch out!
أوفن-ساما، احذر
Knock it off!
توقف
Minister Oven!
أوفن-ساما
What's going on?
ما الذي يحدث هناك؟
Who is that-rero ?
من يكون ذلك الشخص-ريرو؟
Is he Minister Oven's archnemesis?
أهو عدو لدود لأوفن-ساما؟
Pound!
باوند
Y-You're quite tough...
إ-إنّك قوي للغاية
You bastard!
أيها اللعين
Are you... trying to kill your stepson?!
أتحاول قتل ابن زوجتك؟
Father! The water's temperature is falling!
فاذر، درجة حرارة المياه تنخفض
Fold up the paddles! Let's use this chance to push past the hot water!
استخدموا المجاديف، لنخرج من هذه المنطقة الساخنة حالًا
Yes, sir!
حاضر
Let's hurry up and get out of here!
لنخرج من هنا بسرعة
Yes, madam!
حاضر يا سيدتنا
To my grandson, whose name I don't even know...
حفيدي الذي لا أعرف اسمه حتّى
Are you happy?
هل أنت سعيد؟
Make your mommy and daddy love you as much as possible...
دع أباك وأمك يعتنيان بك
I couldn't do that for my children...
فأنا لم أستطع الاعتناء بأطفالي
Not yet? Not yet?
ليس بعد؟ ليس بعد؟
Linlin, you gave birth!
لينلين، لقد أنجبتِ
Yeah... Lola and Chiffon...
أجل، لولا وشيفون
They're twins.
إنّهما توأم
Twins?! I wanna hold them.
توأم؟ أريد حملهما
You've already served your purpose.
لقد انتهى دورك بالفعل
Go away.
ارحل
What?
ماذا؟
Linlin?
لينلين؟
What do you mean?!
عمّ تتحدثين؟
I'm their father! We're...
...أنا والدهما، نحن
You think they're your family? Don't overestimate yourself.
أتود قول «عائلة»؟ لا تبالغ في تقدير نفسك
Linlin!
لينلين
Those are my children!
إنّهما طفلتاي
Please!
أرجوكِ
I wanna hold them at least once!
أودّ أن أحملهما مرة واحدة على الأقل
Linlin!
لينلين
They're... my children...
إنّهما طفلتاي
That was 26 years ago...
كان ذلك قبل 26 عامًا
Chiffon... I'm glad I got to see you at least once.
شيفون، أنا مسرور لرؤيتكِ
It seems like you're being chased,
يبدو أنّكِ مطاردة لسببٍ ما
but I'm glad that you look happy...
لكنني مسرورٌ لرؤيتكِ سعيدة
What's the matter, Pez?
ما الخطب يا بيز؟
You'll be fine! We'll be out of this hot sea soon!
لا تقلق، سنخرج من هذه المياه الساخنة قريبًا
There's nothing to be afraid of!
لا يوجد شيء يدعو للخوف
Stop, Mama!
توقفي يا ماما
Shut up!
اصمتي
Why did I give birth to twins?!
لماذا أنجبتُ توأمًا؟
You're probably a failure just like Lola!
لا بدّ أنّكِ مجرّد فاشلة مثل لولا
Stop!
توقفي
Children who are useless to me aren't part of my family!
الأطفال الذين لا يفيدونني ليسوا جزءًا من عائلتي
Don't you dare show your face around me!
إيّاكِ أن تُريني وجهك
It's going to be all right. Your Papa and Mama are right here.
لا بأس، أبوك وأمك سيبقيان بجانبك دائمًا
I've been worried about you this whole time.
لطالما كنتُ قلقًا عليكِ
Did you go through any hardships?
هل مررتِ بأيام عصيبة؟
Were you ever lonely?
هل مررتِ بأيام شعرتِ فيها بالوحدة؟
I'm sorry that I couldn't be there for you on those days...
أعتذر لعدم وجودي بجانبكِ في تلك الأيام
I know I'm late...
أعلم أنّ هذا متأخر
but I wanted to tell you something.
...لكن دعيني أقول لكِ
Congratulations...
...تهانينا
on your marriage!
...على زواجكِ
Chiffon!
يا شيفون
What?!
ماذا؟
We escaped-rero !
لقد خرجنا-ريرو
Keep going at this speed and escape!
لنواصل على هذا المنوال حتّى نفقدهم
The cake barely survived.
الكعكة بالكاد نجت مما حصل
Let's hurry up! We don't have much time!
لنسرع، فالوقت يداهمنا
Let's begin the decorating!
سنبدأ بتزيين الكعكة
– Okay! – Yeah!
حاضر - أجل -
The Sunny, At Sea
سفينة الساني في البحر
I found you!
عثرتُ عليكم
Hand over the cake!
أعطوني الكعكة
B-B... B-B-Big Mom?!
بـ-بـ-بـ-بيغ مام؟
No matter how you look at it, she's too strong for us!
مهما نظرنا إلى الأمر، فنحن لسنا ندًّا لها
What should we do?!
ما العمل؟
Maybe it'd be best to run...
ربما يجدر بنا مواصلة الهرب
If we stop, that'll be the end! We need to get away somehow!
سيُقضى علينا إن توقفنا، لنواصل الهرب
Here we go!
هيّا بنا
I'll go first!
سأذهب أولًا
I'll get them!
أنا من سيقضي عليهم
Huh? Who's our enemy?
ماذا؟ من عدونا؟
It's the Straw Hat crew!
إنّهم طاقم قبعة القش
Oh, that's right! But I don't see a straw hat anywhere!
هكذا إذًا، لكنني لا أرى أي قبعات قش
Excuse me! Where is the Straw Hat crew?
لو سمحتم، أين طاقم قبعة القش؟
They went that way!
ذهبوا من ذلك الاتجاه
What?!
ماذا؟
Let's go! It's that way!
لنذهب إلى ذلك الاتجاه
Thanks for the directions!
شكرًا على وصفك
Ah! We can't fly that far!
لا يمكنني التقدم أكثر
What were they?
ماذا يكونون؟
I have no idea.
لا أعلم
You idiots!
أيها الحمقى
Why are all of the cannonballs so useless?!
لماذا كل تلك القذائف لم تجدِ نفعًا؟
What's going on?!
ما الذي يحدث؟
As you know, when Mama's out of control, they don't listen to us!
الأمر وما فيه، أنّ القذائف تصبح طائشة عندما تفقد ماما رشدها
Please let me go next!
أطلقوني عليهم
No, I'm next!
كلا، بل أنا
Sir Bavarois! I'll show you that I can do it!
بافروا-ساما، يمكنني فعلها
Charlotte Bavarois 26th Son of the Charlotte Family
الابن 26 لعائلة شارلوت شارلوت بافروا
Damn...
سحقًا
Mama hasn't slowed down, and we're at full speed, too!
لم تخفض ماما من سرعتها، ونحن نُبحر بأقصى سرعة بدورنا
Why can't we catch up to them?!
فلماذا لا نستطيع اللحاق بهم؟
Well, they have Jinbe, who knows the seas like the back of his hand.
الأمر وما فيه، أنّ لديهم جينبي الذي يعرف كل شيء عن البحر
Sir Bavarois! We just got a call!
بافروا-ساما، وردنا اتصال للتو
Here they come!
ها قد وصلوا
Everyone!
يا رفاق
What's the matter, Carrot?!
ما الأمر يا كاروت؟
There are a bunch of ships ahead!
ثمة مجموعة من السفن أمامنا
What?!
ماذا قلتِ؟
Oh, no! We've been pincered!
اللعنة، لقد حاصرونا
Wedding cake!
كعكة الزفاف
Gear Third!
المحرك الثالث غير ثيرد
We just started up again. Don't be so erratic.
أتيتَ وأنت أكثر مشاكسة من ذي قبل
Even if you had escaped earlier, I am your opponent.
لو أنّك اكتفيت بمواصلة الهرب لم يكن ليتجرأ أحد على لومك بما أنني خصمك
So why did you come back?
فلماذا عُدت؟
Did you choose death over the shame of running away?
هل فضّلت اختيار الموت على عار الهرب؟
"Choose death"?
اخترت الموت؟
Or did you notice the difference in our power
أم أدركت أنّك لست ندًّا لي وأتيت لتتوسّل لتصبح أحد حلفائنا؟
"Beg"?
أتوسّل؟
Cut the crap...
هراء
I...
...أنا
came here to beat you!
أتيتُ لهزيمتك
"Came here to beat me"?
أتيت لهزيمتي؟
That is not...
...محالٌ أن يكون
an option!
هذا الخيار متاحًا
Damn...
سحقًا
Before we were able to get Big Mom and the others off of our tail, our path out of here was blocked!
قبل أن نتخلّص من مطاردة بيغ مام والآخرين خلفنا نجد أنفسنا محاصرين من الأمام أيضًا
Sir Bavarois!
بافروا-ساما
Minister Daifuku and his fleet have arrived just up ahead!
أسطول يقوده دايفوكو-ساما قد وصل أمامنا
Charlotte Daifuku 3rd Son of the Charlotte Family
الابن الثالث لعائلة شارلوت شارلوت دايفوكو
And we have reinforcements from behind!
ولدينا تعزيزات من الخلف
From behind?
الخلف؟
That's...
...ذلك
A fleet of reinforcements led by
أسطول من التعزيزات تقوده قائدة الحلوى سموذي-ساما قد وصل للتو
Sweet Commander Smoothie 14th Daughter of the Charlotte Family
الابنة 14 لعائلة شارلوت قائدة الحلوى شارلوت سموذي
Not to mention, Commander Smoothie's flag ship has
إضافة إلى ذلك، السفينة القيادية التي تترأسها سموذي-ساما
Citron 15th Daughter of the Charlotte Family Cinnamon 16th Daughter of the Charlotte Family
الابنة 16 لعائلة شارلوت شارلوت سينامون الابنة 15 لعائلة شارلوت شارلوت سترون
Mistresses Citron and Mistress Cinnamon on board!
على متنها سترون-ساما وسينامون-ساما أيضًا
They're going that far?!
كل أولئك؟
But with them, we'll be invincible!
لكننا لا نقهر في ظل وجودهم
All right. Let's do it, men!
عظيم، هيّا بنا يا رجال
Yeah!
أجل
Hey, Brother Peros, why is it taking so long for you to eliminate one little mouse?
ويحك يا أخي بيروس لِمَ تستغرق كل هذا الوقت للقضاء على ضعفاء؟
Can I just sink them?
أيمكنني إغراقهم وحسب؟
Do whatever you want. Lick...
افعل ما تشاء-بيرورين
You guys are so dramatic!
لقد تباهيتم بأنفسكم كثيرًا
It doesn't matter what happens
ستذهب ماما إلى جزيرة الكاكاو حيث تنتظرها بودينغ
It looks like Mama's getting thinner.
يبدو أنّ ماما أصبحت أنحف-بيرورين
Wedding cake!
كعكة الزفاف
All ships, prepare to fire!
فلتستعد جميع السفن لإطلاق النار
As soon as their ship comes within shooting range,
بمجرّد أن تدخل سفينتهم نطاق تصويبكم
let them have it!
أغرقوها
This is bad...
مصيبة
Daifuku's ships are preparing to fire their cannons!
سفن دايفوكو تتأهب للإطلاق
I don't think we're in their range yet...
لا أظننا في نطاق تصويبهم بعد
Even if we try to dodge, we're surrounded on all sides.
حتّى لو تحركنا جانبًا، فسيحاصروننا من جميع الجهات
Jinbe, let's keep advancing without slowing down!
جينبي، لنستمر بالتقدّم إلى الأمام دون إبطاء سرعتنا
But we're up against Daifuku's ship... He controls a jinni and is a formidable opponent!
لكننا نواجه سفينة دايفوكو الذي يتحكم بالمارد ويصعب التغلّب عليه
We have no choice but to force our way through the front!
لإيجاد مخرج من هذا الوضع، علينا التقدم للأمام
Right. Let's prepare ourselves.
أجل، لنستعد
I'll start this off by taking a rumble ball! Get me close enough to jump onto their ship!
سأتناول كرة رمبل، لذا دع السفينة تقترب من سفينتهم لأتمكن من القفز إليها
Fighting at close range... It's gonna be tough.
القتال قريب المدى سيكون صعبًا
Mm-hm.
أجل
Let's go!
هيّا بنا
They'll be in range soon.
سيدخلون نطاق تصويبنا قريبًا
Fire all of our cannonballs at them.
وحينها أطلقوا كل القذائف نحوهم
Yeah!
أجل
This is our chance!
إنّها فرصتنا
Hey, use the faceless cannonballs.
استخدموا قذائف بلا وجوه
– No way! – Minister Daifuku!
محال
Shut up!
اخرسوا
Chobro!
تشونيكي
Everyone!
رفاق
Let me handle Daifuku and the others!
دعوني أتولى أمر دايفوكو ومن معه
I'll definitely be useful!
واثقة من مقدرتي على المساعدة
Carrot?!
كاروت؟
Because...
...لأنّ الليلة
tonight's a full moon...
القمر مكتمل
Don't tell me... Sulong?! Are you trained for it?! "Sulong": moon lion
سولونغ = أسد القمر أيعقل أنّكِ ستتحولين إلى سولونغ؟ هل تدربتِ على ذلك؟
Don't worry... Pedro trained me.
لا تقلق، لقد دربني بيدرو
I know what Pedro would say right now...
:ما كان سيقوله بيدرو في موقفٍ كهذا
"Leave it to me."
«دعي الأمر لي»
If Carrot is going, I'm going with her!
سأذهب برفقة كاروت إذا عزمت على الذهاب
Leave it to me, Chobro!
دع الأمر لي يا تشونيكي
I'm still a musketeer, after all!
فأنا واحدة من الفرسان بالنهاية
Everyone, man the cannons!
جهزوا المدافع
We'll shoot salvos and sink it quickly!
سنطلق في اللحظة نفسها ونغرق سفينتهم
Wait for my cue!
انتظروا إشارتي
What do you mean, Pedro?
ماذا تعني يا بيدرو؟
One day, you'll see how important it was
يومًا ما، ستدركين مدى أهمية إنقاذ لوفي وطاقمه هنا ومساعدتهم على الإبحار
I'll fight...
...سأقاتل
Pedro!
يا بيدرو
What is that?
ما هذا؟
Her eyes are red... She looks like a different person...
عياناها حمراواتان، تبدو مختلفة تمامًا
Carrot... She's so beautiful...
كاروت... ما أجملك
How mystical...
يا له من منظر مبهر
Oh, she looks pretty amazing...
تبدو خلّابة للغاية
I'd like to see her panties...
كم أود أن أرى ملابسها الداخلية
But after that battle,
...عندما قاتلنا فعلًا
this was the result we had against Jack's squad, a subset of Kaido's army.
كانت هذه هي النتيجة ضد طاقم جاك الذي كان فقط جزءًا من جيش كايدو
But we won't let that happen again! We will not repeat the same mistake!
لكننا لن ندع ذلك يحدث مجدّدًا، لن يتكرر فشلنا
We have our trump card.
فلدينا ورقة رابحة في كفتنا
If we fight them again, we'll show them the true power of the minks!
إن قاتلناهم مجدّدًا، فسنريهم القوة الحقيقية لعشيرة المينك
This must be the trump card he was talking about...
لا بدّ من أنّها الورقة الرابحة التي كان يتحدث عنها آنذاك
The minks'...
...القوة الحقيقية
true power!
لعشيرة المينك
D-Don't tell me that's...
...أ-أيعقل أنّ ذلك
This is bad, Minister Daifuku!
مصيبة يا دايفوكو-ساما
Tonight's a full moon! That mink girl that's with the enemy...
إنّ القمر مكتمل الليلة، وفتاة ...المينك التي في صفوف العدو
turned Sulong!
تحولت إلى سولونغ
Guys! Prepare for a close-quarters battle!
يا رجال، تأهبوا لاشتباك قريب المدى
If I'm correct, Pedro was from Zou, the phantom city...
إن لم تخنِّ الذاكرة، فبيدرو كان من الجزيرة الوهمية زو
I guess she's from the same place...
أظنها تنتمي من المكان نفسه
She's gonna fall into the sea!
ستسقط في البحر
Huh?! What the...
ماذا؟ ما هذا؟
She just flew up from the surface!
لقد طارت فوق سطح البحر للتو
Amazing...
مذهل
That's not all...
ما زال الوقت باكرًا لتأخذكم الدهشة
Here she comes! Shoot her down!
إنّها قادمة، أسقطوها
Yes, sir!
حاضر
Don't lower your guard!
لا ترخوا دفاعكم
She's a warrior from Zou! They're on a different level!
إنّها محاربة من زو، فهم شديدي الصرامة
I'll bring her down!
سأسقطها
What?!
ماذا؟
Don't hold back! Take her out!
لا تتراجعوا، أسقطوها
Damn! Shoot!
سحقًا، أطلقوا
I've got you!
نلتُ منك
Hey!
...أخبرني
What's going on? Chopper!
ما الذي يجري يا تشوبر؟
Damn little rat!
أيتها الفتاة اللعينة
Do you plan on fighting all of the soldiers in this fleet in order to stop us?!
هل ستردعين سفننا عبر هزيمة جميع جنود أسطولنا؟
While you're doing that, your ship will sink! Stop your futile resistance and–
...سفينتكم اللعينة ستغرق أثناء قيامك بذلك، لذا لا جدوى من
The helm?!
الدفة؟
S-She broke the helm!
لـ-لقد اقتلعت الدفة
Oh, no! Where is our ship heading?!
مصيبة، إلى أين تتجه هذه السفينة؟
That little rat!
أيتها اللعينة